{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","address":"5163 Trumbull Ave","zipcode":"48208","owner":"Jeremy Damaske","licenseNumber":"203366","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":null,"establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Plan Review","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000D852E86B1FC554C068C2A5B94E2D4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44268","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","inspectionDate":"2018-11-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44268","inspectionDate":"11/29/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the Shelves","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"},{"inspectionid":"44268","inspectionDate":"11/29/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Cold holding equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"44268","inspectionDate":"11/29/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Three compartment sink","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]},{"inspectionid":"42214","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","inspectionDate":"2018-05-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42214","inspectionDate":"5/15/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Inside the Walk-in freezer","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"42214","inspectionDate":"5/15/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly date marked","subProblem":"Longer than 7 days stored at 41 degrees f After preparation","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Shelf","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide proper date marks as stated above."},{"inspectionid":"42214","inspectionDate":"5/15/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","violationCode":"5-203.14","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be installed to preclude backflow of contaminants into the water supply system at each point of use at the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT by providing an air gap or installing an APPROVED backflow prevention device. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow prevention","subItem":"backflow/backsiphonage device vacuum breaker","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"PATIO","subLocation":"At the Hose spigot","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"42214","inspectionDate":"5/15/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Cooler (pizza-prep)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"40384","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","inspectionDate":"2017-10-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"38187","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","inspectionDate":"2017-03-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"127","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38187","inspectionDate":"3/8/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."}]},{"inspectionid":"36341","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","inspectionDate":"2016-08-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36341","inspectionDate":"8/31/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","violationCode":"4-501.19","violationDescription":"The temperature of the wash solution in manual WAREWASHING EQUIPMENT shall be maintained at not less than 110 F or the temperature specified on the cleaning agent manufacturer's label instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Manual warewash wash solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 110 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Change water frequently to maintain at least 110 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"36341","inspectionDate":"8/31/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"inspectionid":"36341","inspectionDate":"8/31/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"36341","inspectionDate":"8/31/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5156","name":"Pie-Sci Pizza","violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5156"}}